export const quizData = {
  "Throne": [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: {
        key: "what_animal_rowan",
        en: `What animal Rowan turns into?`,
      },
      options: {
        en: [`panther`, `hawk`, `wolf`, `dragonfly`]
      },
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: `What’s the real name of Celaena Sardothien?`,
      options: [`Aelin Ashryver Whitethorn Galathynius`, `Aelin Ashriver Whitethorn Galathynius`, `Lysandra Ashryver née Ennar`, `Aelin Ashryver Ennar Galathynius`],
      answer: `Aelin Ashryver Whitethorn Galathynius`
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: `Where Aelin was born?`,
      options: [`Orynth`, `Rifthold`, `Eyllwe`, `Varese`],
      answer: `Orynth`
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: `How old is Dorian in the first volume of Throne of Glass series?`,
      options: [`20`, `27`, `17`, `19`],
      answer: `19`
    },
      {
      id: 5,
      question: `What’s the name of Aelin’s dog?`,
      options: [`Fire`, `Fleetfoot`, `Arrowhead`, `Tulip`],
      answer: `Fleetfoot`
    },
      {
      id: 6,
      question: `What is Lysandra's occupation?`,
      options: [`assassin`, `carter`, `courtesan`, `baker`],
      answer: `courtesan`
    },
      {
      id: 7,
      question: `Who is the first character mentioned by name in Heir of Fire?`,
      options: [`Chaol Westfall`, `Dorian Havilliard`, `Celaena Sardothien`, `Aelin Galathynius`],
      answer: `Celaena Sardothien`
    },
      {
      id: 8,
      question: `What is the capital of Adarlan?`,
      options: [`Rifthold`, `Orynth`, `Varese`, `Meah`],
      answer: `Rifthold`
    },
      {
      id: 9,
      question: `What clan does Asterin belong to?`,
      options: [`Yellowlegs`, `Fleetfoot`, `Purebloods`, `Blackbeaks`],
      answer: `Blackbeaks`
    },
      {
      id: 10,
      question: `Where do the Thirteen stay and work in Queen of Shadows?`,
      options: [`Meah`, `Rifthold`, `Morath`, `Varese`],
      answer: `Morath`
    },
      {
      id: 11,
      question: `What was the name of Rowan's wife?`,
      options: [`Lyria`, `Mab`, `Lysandra`, `Lyvia`],
      answer: `Lyria`
    },
      {
      id: 12,
      question: `How many members does Cadre have in Heir of Fire?`,
      options: [`8`, `4`, `6`, `12`],
      answer: `6`
    },
      {
      id: 13,
      question: `What eye color does Elide have?`,
      options: [`onyx`, `emerald`, `grey`, `amber`],
      answer: `onyx`
    },
      {
      id: 14,
      question: `What is the name of Aedion's sword?`,
      options: [`Sword of Orynth`, `Morath`, `Goldryn`, `Damaris`],
      answer: `Sword of Orynth`
    },
    {
      id: 15,
      question: `What is Dorian's fathers name?`,
      options: [`Hollin`, `Brannon`, `Dorian`, `Chaol`],
      answer: `Dorian`
    }
  ],

  "Harry": [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: `What spell did Hermione use to help the Gringotts dragon escape, carving a passageway in the ceiling?`,
      options: [`Relashio`, `Defodio`, `Episkey`, `Reducto`],
      answer: `Defodio`
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: `What's Ginny Weasley's star sign?`,
      options: [`Virgio`, `Leo`, `Gemini`, `Libra`],
      answer: `Leo`
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: `What is Harry Potter's birthday?`,
      options: [`December 24th`, `July 24th`, `July 31st`, `September 13th`],
      answer: `July 31st`
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: `What was the first task of the Triwizard Tournament?`,
      options: [`Wizard Dueling`, `Fighting a Dragon`, `Wizard's Chess`, `a Maze`],
      answer: `Fighting a Dragon`
    },
      {
      id: 5,
      question: `In quidditch, how many points is the golden Snitch worth?`,
      options: [`150`, `200`, `100`, `120`],
      answer: `150`
    },
      {
      id: 6,
      question: `Dumbledore has a scar on his knee. What does the scar picture?`,
      options: [`Hogwarts`, `the London Underground`, `his mother`, `his siblings`],
      answer: `the London Underground`
    },
      {
      id: 7,
      question: `What was different about the students that were petrified by the Basilisk?`,
      options: [`There was nothing different about them`, `They were all Halfblood`, `They were all Mudbloods`, `They were all Pureblood`],
      answer: `They were all Mudbloods`
    },
      {
      id: 8,
      question: `What spell does Lockhart accidentally cast on himself in the Chamber of Secrets?`,
      options: [`Lumos`, `Obliviate`, `Sectumsempra`, `Avada Kedavra`],
      answer: `Obliviate`
    },
      {
      id: 9,
      question: `What is Draco's middle name?`,
      options: [`Lucius`, `Harry`, `Salazar`, `Riddle`],
      answer: `Lucius`
    },
      {
      id: 10,
      question: `Who is Harry's least favorite professor?`,
      options: [`Flitwick`, `Voldemort`, `Snape`, `Sprout`],
      answer: `Snape`
    }
  ],

  "Twilight": [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: `What instrument does Edward play?`,
      options: [`Piano`, `Violin`, `Drums`, `Guitar`],
      answer: `Piano`
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: `What class did Bella and Edward take together Junior year?`,
      options: [`Biology`, `Spanish`, `Chemistry`, `Trigonometry`],
      answer: `Biology`
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: `Which vampire was NOT turned by Carlisle Cullen?`,
      options: [`Alice`, `Edward`, `Jasper`, `Esme`],
      answer: `Jasper`
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: `What's Edward's favourite animal to hunt?`,
      options: [`Grizzly Bears`, `Mountain Lion`, `Cat`, `Deer`],
      answer: `Mountain Lion`
    },
      {
      id: 5,
      question: `Who became a werewolf first?`,
      options: [`Jacob`, `Paul`, `Jared`, `Sam`],
      answer: `Sam`
    },
      {
      id: 6,
      question: `According to the books, who did James meet first?`,
      options: [`Alice`, `Edward`, `Carlise`, `Jasper`],
      answer: `Alice`
    },
      {
      id: 7,
      question: `What frustrates Edward about Bella?`,
      options: [`She smells bad`, `She plays dumb in class`, `He can't read her mind`, `She acts like she's the best`],
      answer: `He can't read her mind`
    },
      {
      id: 8,
      question: `What do vampires really need in order to play baseball?`,
      options: [`Old-timey uniforms`, `Thunder`, `Aluminum bats`, `Rubber baseballs`],
      answer: `Thunder`
    },
      {
      id: 9,
      question: `What part of Bella is bitten by James?`,
      options: [`Wrist`, `Nose`, `Middle finger`, `Leg`],
      answer: `Wrist`
    },
      {
      id: 10,
      question: `How old is Edward supposed to be in the book?`,
      options: [`16`, `17`, `2`, `18`],
      answer: `17`
    }
  ],

  "Hunger": [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: `How did Katniss’s father die?`,
      options: [`In a hunting accident`, `In a mine explosion`, `He became trapped in a collapsed mine`, `He was murdered by the Capitol`],
      answer: `In a mine explosion`
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: `At what skill is Gale better than Katniss?`,
      options: [`Cooking`, `Using an axe`, `Setting snares`, `Swimming`],
      answer: `Setting snares`
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: `Who gives Katniss the mockingjay pin?`,
      options: [`Madge`, `Gale`, `Peeta`, `Prim`],
      answer: `Madge`
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: `Under what circumstances did Katniss first meet Peeta?`,
      options: [`Katniss was looking for food and Peeta gave her bread`, `At the Hunger Games`, `They were both in the woods hunting`, `Peeta was injured and Katniss’s mother helped him`],
      answer: `Katniss was looking for food and Peeta gave her bread`
    },
      {
      id: 5,
      question: `Which training station does Peeta excel at?`,
      options: [`Archery`, `Knife throwing`, `Knot tying`, `Camouflage`],
      answer: `150`
    },
      {
      id: 6,
      question: `What is the first thing Katniss looks for after running from the Cornucopia?`,
      options: [`Food`, `Water`, `Shelter`, `Fire`],
      answer: `Water`
    },
      {
      id: 7,
      question: `What’s the name of the day when tributes are chosen?`,
      options: [`Harvesting Day`, `Reaping Day`, `Threshing Day`, `Selection Day`],
      answer: `Reaping Day`
    },
      {
      id: 8,
      question: `What is an Avox missing?`,
      options: [`Tongue`, `Heart`, `Nose`, `Eyes`],
      answer: `Tongue`
    }
  ]
};
  